bitbay.net 2018-04-18

# Privacy Policy - Bitcoin Exchange | BitBay

##  I. Definitions 

  1. Administrator - the Administrator of personal data within the meaning of the Act of 29 August 1997 on personal data protection (consolidated text. Laws of 2002, No. 101, item. 926, as amended) which is the Bit Bay limited liability company with its registered office in Katowice at Zacisze 2/6, 40-025 Katowice, entered in the register of the National Court Register kept by the Regional Court WARSAW, XII Commercial Division of the National Court Register under the number KRS 0000373405 with registered capital of 100,000.00 PLN, NIP 7010274151, ID 14273486.
  2. Personal Data - personal data of users is being kept for the reason of using the service.
  3. Site operator - Bit Bay limited liability company with its registered office in Katowice at Zacisze 2/6, 40-025 Katowice, entered in the register of the National Court Register kept by the Regional Court WARSAW, XII Commercial Division of the National Court Register under the number KRS 0000373405 with registered capital of 100,000.00 PLN, NIP 7010274151, ID 14273486.
  4. The site is being available online at the domain www.bitbay.pl.
  5. Services - services being provided by the site, especially intermediary of sale and purchase of crypto currency. User - user of the website. 

##  II. General Information. 

* The platform performs the functions of obtaining information about the Users and their behavior as follows: 

  * By voluntarily entered information into interactive forms.
  * By storing terminal devices files (called "cookies").
  * By collecting web server logs. 

##  III. Rules of collecting user's personal data

* Using the website requires Users to share their Personal Data. Failing to do so prevents the use of the Services.
* Service collects the information provided voluntarily by the User.
* Moreover, the service can save the connection settings (marking time, IP address).
* DData collected from users is not shared with third parties, unless: 

  * User agrees to do so
  * This will be justified by the law
  * It will be necessary i order to provide the Services, in particular concerning technical support, processing payments or others. 

## IV. Scope of personal data and processing of personal data

* To the extent justified by a particular service, Administrator may ask the User to share following personal information: first name, last name, address, series and number of ID, national identification number. 

## V. User rights

* User is allowed to access their personal data, to amend and update it.
* The user is entitled to request amendments, updates, clarifications of their personal data, temporary or permanent suspension or deleting if it is incomplete, outdated, untrue r collected in violation of the law or is no longer required for the purpose for which it was collected.
* In the event of a change of any Personal Data , User is obliged to perform activities aimed to update Personal Data in their account.
* The User have the right to delete their Personal Data at any time.
* Administrator may refuse to remove Personal Data if the User fails to pay all amounts owed to the Administrator or violates the Terms of Service r any applicable law and the preservation of personal data is necessary to examine these circumstances and determine the responsibilities of the user. 

## VI. Information on cookie files

* The website is using cookies.
* Cookies are computer data, especially small text files, that are stored on the User’s terminal equipment and are intended for the usage of the Site. Cookies typically contain the name of the website, storage time for a terminal device and a unique number.
* Entity storing cookies on the device belonging to the end user and reaching an access to them is the operator of the website.
* Cookies are being used for the following purposes: 

  * creating statistics that help to understand how the Service Users benefit from web pages, which allows to improve their structure and content
  * maintenance of the Service User's session ( after logging in), by which user does not have to retype login and password at every sub-site
  * determining a user profile in order to display matched materials coming from advertising platforms, particularly the Google Network.

* The website uses two basic types of cookies: session cookies and fixed cookies. Session cookies are temporary files that are stored in the terminal equipment of a user until the time they log out, leave the website or disable the software ( web browser). Permanent cookies are stored in the terminal equipment of a user for the time specified in the parameters of cookies or until their removal by the user.
* Software used for browsing the web ( browser) usually by default allows cookies to be stored on the end user device. Service Users can change these settings. Internet browser enables user to delete cookies. User can also automatically block cookies details, in order to learn how to do this they should see help or documentation sections of their web browser.
* Restricting cookies may affect some of the functionality available on the Website.
* Cookies may also be used by companies cooperating with the operator of the Service like advertisers and partners.
* We recommend reading privacy policies of these companies to learn the rules of the use of cookies used in statistics : Privacy Policy Google Analytics. Cookies may be used by ad networks , in particular, the Network Google to display ads tailored to the way in which user uses the Service. They may include information about the user navigation path or the time they stay on the page. In terms of information about user preferences collected by the Google Display Network , you can view and edit information derived from cookies with a tool : https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/ 

##  VII. Server logs 

* Some information concerning users’ behaviour are subject to log into the server layer. This data is used only to administrate the site and to ensure the most efficient hosting services.
* Browsed resources are being identified by URLs. In addition following data may be stored: 

  * date of request,
  * time of reply,
  * name of the client station - identification carried by HTTP , HTTPS,
  * information about errors that occurred during the HTTP, HTTPS transaction,
  * URL of the page previously visited by the user ( reference link ) - where the transition to the Service took place by reference,
  * information about the user's browser,
  * IP address information.

* These figures are not associated with the individual persons, the Administrator does not connect these data with User’s Personal Data and does not use them to identify the user (except when it is necessary for the proper implementation of the Service) , and so the resulting data is used only for the purposes of administering the server.

##  VIII. Cookie files management - how to express and retract permission in practice? 

  1. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may change your browser settings. We reserve that disabling cookies required for authentication processes, security, maintenance, user preferences may make it difficult and in extreme cases may prevent the use of the website.
  2. In order to manage cookie settings select your browser from the list below and follow the instructions: 
    * Internet Explorer
    * Chrome
    * Safari
    * Firefox
    * Opera
    * Android
    * Safari(iOS)
    * Windows Phone
    * Blackberry 

##  IX. Contact 

* User can contact Administrator anytime in order to get the following information: 

  * about aims, scope and ways of processing data included in such a range,
  * how long is the user’s data being processed. It is also possible to preview all the data in a widely understandable format,
  * about source from which the website posses their data, unless the administrator is obliged to keep this information as a secret,
  * about sharing data and categories of data recipients.

* Address where you can contact the Administrator: support@bitbay.net
